RG 002:025, Human Services Committee
Connecticut State Library
Committee on Human Services records
1987-1997
Connecticut State Library 231 Capitol Avenue Hartford, Connecticut, 06106-1537
Connecticut. General Assembly. Committee on Human Services
.5 cubic feet
Human Services Committee meeting material.
RG002_025_HUM
Multiple
Scope and Content
These records contain meeting material that include notices, agendas, attendance sheets, minutes, and transcripts.
Arrangement
Arranged by accession.
Index Terms
Organizations:
Connecticut. General Assembly. Committee on Human Services
Subjects:
Block grants -- Connecticut; Public welfare -- Connecticut; Connecticut. General Assembly. Committee on Human Services -- Records and correspondence; Poor -- Energy assistance -- Connecticut -- Finance
Document Types:
Agendas; Membership lists; Minutes; Reports; Transcripts
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Accession: 1999-075, 1991; 1 folder
  - Meeting material, 1991
    Includes roll call sheets; committee meeting attendance sheets; public hearing attendance sheets; meeting notices, 1991 February-April; agendas, 1991 January-September; minutes, 1991 January-May
- Accession: 2001-045, 1987; 3 folders
  - Meeting to review Governor's amendments to Enery Assistance Block Grant, 1987 December 15
    Includes attendence sheet, meeting notice, briefing.
  - Meeting on Community Servcice Block Grant, 1987 July 30
    Includes transcript, minutes, attendance.
  - Meeting on Energy Assistance Block Grant, 1987 July 20, 22
    Includes meeting notice, minutes, attendance sheet, transcript, meeting material, and a report on Connecticut Energy Assistance Program, 10/1/987-11/30/87
  - Meeting on Social Services Block Grant, 1987 September 28
    Includes attendance sheet, minutes, roll call, meeting material, transcript
    In same folder as meeting above on Energy Assistance Block Grant
- Accession: 2001-051, 1994; 1 folder
  - Meeting material, 1994
    Includes attendence sheets, list of bills, membership list
- Accession: 2010-043, 1997 April 3
  Transcript and audio cassettes of meeting